[Music]
Now I want to acknowledge the
hard work she and
her team have put into organizing this event for us,
and without them, we wouldn't have a
program. Can the whole
team please stand up? The team
early,
the team's team, everyone who helped,
all the volunteers.
[Music]
Thank you so much.
And on the American side,
I want to thank the team and the turnaround. Thank you so much.
[Music]
[Applause]
We've been together for eight days now.
I know many of you have flown from very far away.
Thank you for coming.
It's time to find and come here.
It's about coming to
stay, and I'm very grateful that
you came.
In this program in Thailand, she had
a good idea.
She said, "Let's ask people to bring
their parents
and their children too.
People can have
a family drama vacation there." And that
's a very nice idea.
I think later in our lives, that's
the time we
can remember when we use the time to spend with
our parents together.  I've spent time here.
I'm very grateful that you had this idea,
and I would ask the parents to please stand up for a moment.
Thank you.
[Applause]
[Music]
The children had to hand it out. The children
also receive it in a bubble.
[Music]
The children from Moscow
learn the program today and every day for three and a half hours in the morning.
Usually, I did this three or four times a day. During the day,
and in the afternoon, everyone gets tired,
and that's why I decided we should have
one long class in the morning.
You are fresh, and I am also fresh. If
you want a long class in the morning, it
's a good time to meditate.
But we take a long break in the
morning. Don't worry,
we don't
usually sit like this. Today, you're
fresh, but after three days,
you'll be back. It's just that you...
This is very important.
You can't
get this anywhere else. These teachers will help you
throughout your life. This will also help you
after you die, and that's
different from other lectures. The learning... and
that's very...  It's important, an important
time for all of us again,
sometimes it will still be a problem to get a hotel room,
sometimes you'll
miss your refrigerator at home, a
relaxed helper, just consumption, more relaxed,
and listen, open
your heart. They have just
returned from a special program in Munich,
it's for special
business leaders, twelve of them here,
and I would like to think about them too. Do
you also know these questions? Yes
[Applause]
And they also learn about these table ideas
and how to
use them in their company, in business, in their
family. My hope for this
program
[Music]
I don't feel that it's a
religious program. We have people
from Mexico, like many from the cranes here,
from Russia, Germany.
Every country has its own culture,
every country has its own religion.
Mexicans
get married in a church,
in Ukraine also they get married in
an Eastern Christian church, and
we all have our own family
culture, and I think we
should respect this culture.
Mexicans don't want to get married in a
Buddhist church.  Marrying in a temple, their
mother wouldn't appreciate that,
and that's okay. My dream for this
week is that
I don't want to be the religious leader,
and I don't want to be a fanatic.
We're just friends. We'll
learn these ideas
[Music]
that will help us, our ideas that will
help you and us our whole lives.
After you die, they'll still help.
Teachers come and go.
The student will age. Then
the teacher remembers, "I love you. I
love children."
We have many teachers here.
Later, I want you to become teachers.
It's good to respect the teacher,
but not too much. Respect
the teachings,
then you'll be happy. Okay, today I'm
sharing with you what I know.
Maybe you'll do this up here someday.
Just relax, learn these ideas, take
them home,
use them quietly in
different countries and cultures,
and then you will have a happy life.
We usually start with
meditation in the morning because it's still
fresh, and then we have lectures.
It's a very famous, thick
book. My teacher taught it to me.
We lived together for years, like an old
married couple, and he was very good
to me, very loving.
He taught me this book three times,
very slowly.
Each time it took ten years,
reciting it very slowly, savoring every word.
If you think the only good thing about
McDonald's and Kentucky Fried Chicken is that the
meat isn't good for you, okay? They kill
ten billion
chickens every year, I think. But isn't that
the potato, the prophetess, very good? Is
n't it fast enough? Enjoy it.
This clarifies this learning. I
started eight years ago.
We're halfway through now.
I'm chewing the fried
and learning now, and just enjoying it. Just enjoy it,
have fun with it. It's
very important when you
come to this kind of lecture that you go swimming in between.
Too much is too much. Do
n't sleep in class, but enjoy it. Okay,
we're on a ladies' vacation. It's
important to relax. Enjoy it, have fun with it.
We have fun together. Bring a
meditation with me. Everything is okay.
The children can go if they want.
The children are seated.  There are currently nine
children in the class.
I would like to welcome the children's class
teacher, World Turns
Canada. He has many years of experience
[in music].
He also has three years of experience. He
successfully completed his studies
in a small room.
He is a great teacher and
also has a lot of experience teaching
Chinese children. It's great
that he's here. There's
a special meditation
I've been teaching for two or three years now.
Right,
we started it in Mexico. The
group in Mexico has become
teachers. They have
completed 18 courses. It's
bigger now, and now they are learning this, and
I hope you will learn it too. But
we have this meditation. I can tell you about it. We
started it in Mexico. I
have the story now. The
background is a meditation.
I told you about it last time.
It comes from the school. He
lived 1700 years ago. His books are
famous in China, especially Maria Sang's
collection of Hana books. Many of his
books were translated by Swiss people,
mainly by a
Only School representative, and his
books are then...  Most famous thanks, ciao
ciao, and very helpful. He
met my trainer, the future brother,
and he taught them, and Miele taught
this meditation.
CPM,
this meditation should be very short,
to understand a future life.
[Music]
We'll work on that, five parts.
Normally I do one part at a time.
I think you're ready now for
us to do all five parts.
It takes a little more time.
We have it every day, so we'll add one part.
Okay, we'll do this. Now it's time.
Sometimes when I teach meditation,
people quickly sit down on
the floor. We meditate.
We have to do this story here.
Then I say, why is it always like this? On the floor, on the floor. Now
I always say,
you understand, you won't. Why?
2000 years ago there was no silence.
Okay, the study is okay. It's okay
to meditate in a chair.
[Music]
I have an official slogan dance
meditation cushion from Stanley, but I
put the cushion on my couch. It's more
comfortable.
You can meditate in a chair.
Just sit down, your
feet are on the...  Floor straight, across, expensive
wines, not in a
line, sitting on a chair, just straighten
up. When we meditate in a group,
it's very, very important to be silent.
That helps the other people. Mother said
always turn off your
phone first before meditating, and that's
good. Clear your throat now, done.
No more clearing your throat now. Okay,
if you're in the back, you have a
choice. If the room
is a bit cold, put the left one down first
and then the right one. On the
left, in the pictures, is the brother? It looks like this,
but if you say that, it distracts
you from the meditation. If you're
thinking about your thumbs, how to keep the ladies around,
I like it when I can just
relax. Let yourself sit like that, or
if the room is too warm, then you can
do it like this. There are three
choices. You can do it either way.
I like it in between, and it does
n't hurt your wrists. I also have a
three-year list. I
was in a room from 2000 to 2003 and did
n't speak for three years. I
tried everything.
And I've found the right way.
The correct way is the one that works for you. The
correct method is the one that
works for you. Everyone is
different. Everyone has a different body.
Try different things,
and what works for you is fine.
Your body is different from my body.
For example, Michael Merten Butter. I have to sit differently.
Maybe your bottom is medium-sized,
maybe you have a generous
bottom at first, and everyone is different.
It sits the way that suits you.
Try different things
and try to see what works for you.
We begin however
you always do it. It's good if
the first finger and thumb
are close together.
Then the banner closes in a circle, in
a closed circuit.
Trying is not to touch completely.
You can play with how the banner
flows, bringing itself over it.
Try it. We begin.
The face is very relaxed.
Usually, when I meditate and
concentrate,
my shoulders tense up,
and then I have to make sure that
I relax my shoulders.
Many meditation teachers have told me
that the shoulders are too tense.
The moon is relaxed and slightly open. A
slight smile helps.  Flowing towards the burner,
the belly becomes very slightly tensed,
and the standing should be relaxed. The
eyes should be relaxed.
Now we will learn the dance.
We will learn a part of it today.
Usually in meditation,
we begin by observing our breathing,
but in the Lion Dance, we do
n't begin with data.
We begin with a sound in the room. In
this room, we have a
small sound from the air conditioning. Concentrated,
this sound helps you focus your mind. Focus your mind
on this sound. When we
fall asleep in the evening,
we lay our head on the
pillow. In the Lion Dance,
you lay your mind on the sound, just
as you lay your head on the pulse. Let's
begin.
Just listen to the sound. We
begin to concentrate on it.
Now we go deep, so firmly, so
here, to feel your heartbeat,
so that the guests, so also, beat
your heartbeat.
It is we into the heart. The
heart is like a small apartment
in a small room. Imagine
the team heart is inside. The
walls of the heart beat around
you.  It
's not a dark, wet place. They
are very elegant, the small
apartment. The sun comes in through the
windows. It feels
very spacious and open. So,
students, go into the heart now
and enjoy the greater stillness.
We will meditate
for many days. The banner will become stronger and stronger. Sometimes it becomes too intense, too fast. There is a special technique to help prevent the banner from building up too much. I want him to learn it right now because we will meditate for many days.
When you exhale,
the lungs are at the end of the exhalation,
but there is still a little bit of
air left, a little bit of this
sky ending inside. This keeps increasing,
and then you get too much banner,
too much tea. Then you feel nervous. There is
a special method you
can use when you exhale.
When the lungs stop exhaling,
then you can expel a little more
air so that the exhalation
becomes long. Then a pause, and then
exhale a little more.
[Music]
If you are very conscious of your training
and you do this special method,
then you won't get nervous or  You wo
n't, because the chest isn't
constricted,
a walk to the burden that you try for 56
breaths. If you have,
usually at the end of the exhalation, exhale a little
more.
The rest is normal, that you
try it together. If the lungs pause during the
exhalation, then exhale a
little more.
Now we go back to the apartment,
the heart.
Now imagine that the apartment
is a little bigger.
I like to make it a penthouse,
and right at the top under the roof of the
building, there are far too many rooms.
And then I go to the room in the center
[music],
and I don't always meditate there, as there
is a lot of light.
The sound of the turning of the heartbeat sounds a
little further away,
quieter than before.
In this small meditation room, there is
a small table at my side,
and on this table is a small
sugar bowl.
I take the lid off the sugar
bowl and place my finger
on the small one,
and when I take my finger out, there is
a small piece of
crystal on my finger.  My
manager wants my meditation to become
deeper and stronger, so I decide to put
my mind into this tiny
sugar crystal. My mind,
smaller, smaller, and smaller,
a small window opens into the
sugar crystal,
and my mind goes back into this
valley, tiny as a
pinhead. And when I
'm inside the sugar crystal, there's
a surprise because inside
is a very beautiful room, very rich, very expensive,
beautiful wood, many beautiful cushions,
and in very soft sunlight, a
perfect meditation room. And in this
very quiet place, I stay and enjoy it.
And now I gladly open my
mind a little more.
This little sugar crystal
might feel a little tight, urgent,
and then my mind becomes the water of the
Pacific Ocean, and that
expands to the end of this world. Part of
this water touches Thailand, some of it
for China. Part of the water, part of the
water touches California. Enormous,
very far,
very still, active. Imagine the mind.
through always inside sugar crystals
but as far as the Pacific Ocean
still
calm and deep
and now
I like my mind to grow even bigger
and I know it to the sky above
the ocean would expand more when
guest to all the water of the ocean
and half of my mind expands
to the whole blue sky very far very
big is very open very still very
relaxed
[Music]
then please make three deep statements to
Christians don't
forget to exhale even more
after you are finished with the negotiation
then slowly open your eyes then
dirty gladly that is very good so
also something to drink people at the
technical you I need some
microphones for questions
is it important that you have been in
the class your people from many
countries here some people make cool
rooms man today there were more rooms
we will make the room a little cooler
and therefore please bring a scarf
because the air conditioning can make
you feel a little sick because you
bring a scarf please
we will take a break in about ten minutes
a pee break but  If
you have any questions, your
meditation could be this meditation
or other meditations of power,
if you would like to ask a question, then
please point and how to
answer it.
Thank you very much for learning and coming to
the galaxy. I would like to know the benefits of
this meditation.
Good question. This meditation has 29
steps. This is the first step for
taking new steps. What was the
first one? Yes, the air conditioning. They
count for little. That is step number
0.
That's right, the air conditioning is first,
but that's not menstruation. That's
just belonging to the air conditioning. What is
the first step after that? Heartbeat is
the first step.
What then goes into the heart, right into the heart, always. That's
the second step. It's the
third step, into the center, into the
middle of the heart.
It's the fourth step.
Sugar crystals. Fifth ocean. Next
step, the sky.
Made in six parts, 2298. The benefit of this
first eight part is only to bring the mind to more
stillness.
There is no important content that they are
not really important meditations. The
purpose of the  The first eight steps are
practice, training, made for advertising,
trained in it, mind. I believe so
agile because I am the first thing we
have, they are on, but that is not the
game, that is just the warm-up. The
first eight steps are not table tennis, it
is just a warm-up for the
mind. It would be smaller, no,
who, bigger and bigger, with the
sky,
the native, and back to small. That is
a warm-up for the mind.
You can do it like that too, but then
you might lose too much hair, a
little dangerous.
Step number nine is the important
content in the step. We go to
emptying,
we go to past lives, to the
teacher.
These are great advantages, to see directly, to end death.
For many people, to see past lives, to
see
future lives. It is very
important in this world.
Everyone is excited about this life.
I don't earn any money.
I know a girlfriend. I
can get iodine iron.
We are interested in this life,
but it is good to understand what
happens after. It is good to see that directly.
That is good to know where we came from, what
our past life was, that the
purpose after  Coming to Thailand is the
goal. In normal life,
we don't think about past
lives.
We don't think much about future
lives. That's okay.
We have certain obligations. We have to take care of
our children.
We have to take care of our parents. That
's good to focus on this life,
but it's also good to prepare for the future.
If you want to go to Thailand in three days,
then it's
sensible to pack my suitcase now.
Some fans haven't done that. I
haven't done that.
A plane flies away from
Chen Jin at 8. Packing is too stressful, probably too
late.
I also forgot my coffee and a croissant.
It's better if you know
where you're going, what pilgrimage, next
life.
It's better to prepare for it now.
Pack your suitcase three days before
departure, and you can
relax. Then you won't forget anything.
That's the purpose and the
goal of coming to a
normal life, in a normal job.
Focus on family, but parents.
I'm going to Thailand,
pack my  A suitcase
makes a suitcase ready; this is the
time to take care of future lives now;
this is the main advantage; level
number 9 prepares us for future
lives and we will try
to see the majority directly.
n you master directly see head
correct way Christa
throw away the suitcase
can can future life more okay
now his brother okay then you can
help everyone
that is the goal of the apartments one
the first eight are just a warm-
up exercise
if you participate in a table tennis competition
one important e.g. Olympic
Games Stanley has to do a table tennis
competition at 9 o'clock then is
finally in his hotel room gets ready prepares
and then he forgets
to come to play table tennis
everyone is the biggest place what does yes
now is the competition now it starts
the game rather they will be with him in
the hotel room
the topic profession the new point comcom
understands he the apartment new is that because
I am the first eight levels is a
warm-up exercise don't get stuck in the warm-up exercise
that is not poetry is
okay are just the preparation some people
say I will consider my breathing
of the air conditioning to
I have my heart to one hour two
hours
that  Here's the first one, they warmed up, there they were
playing table tennis. Let's take
a break for 15
minutes.
I'm sure a bell will ring. Okay,
thank you, have a nice break.
Okay, now we're starting.
We'll begin now with Lahm, because the
steps on the way... It's a very
famous book. The name of the book, the
title of the book, Alexander, means
freedom, freedom from death, from aging, from suffering,
freedom for the whole world. Of course,
if that's freedom, Stanley,
I say, show me your hand. That's what
the title means. The teacher created
freedom, hello,
give me your hand, goes,
and that's the title of the book.
So, if you study, if you study,
then that you attain this freedom,
and you can also give it to other people
during these 78 days. Now you have
two tasks. Task number one:
accept freedom and keep it,
but also learn how to give it to other
people.
You have a whole... you have a notebook,
and there's a lot of empty space.  And there
you can write your notes
because if you share them with other people,
good notes are also helpful. Don't be like
that famous person who
visited the class for eight days,
and then they went home and
asked him what he had
learned. There was
the Lion Dance meditation, nine
stages.
Oh yes, really. What is the first stage?
I can't remember. What is the
second stage? It's not that important. What is
the third stage? I think it was the sea. I'm
not sure if it really is the
sea.
No, that's number five.
So really, write things down, take
notes because if
someone asks you a question, then
you can help them.
We also have very special
review classes.
I've been teaching Lamb Rim for
eight years now, and we will have special
review classes. So every
day I help you review the previous
content, and thanks to that, there are
special groups for
reviewing the previous content.
But I'll repeat one thing to you now:
when you go home and people
ask you what you studied, the
new stages of meditation, and they ask you
Ask what the new levels are,
and then he says, "Okay, I'll look it up.
I took good notes because the
Bachelor asked us to take good notes.
Then you can really share it
with your friends. Take notes,
and then meet up with
your friends at the café and share it with
them. Two things happen when you
share it with your friends:
all the brothers from all universes come
and watch you. When you're at the café
and you share it with your friends,
it gets very crowded because so
many Butter Star characters are there, and they're
happy about it, like they're so
proud of your parents.
Kukksi is at the café with her friend,
and let us hear that
she teaches the new levels
pretty well. We're happy about it
every time someone
shares it with other people. Then the
Buddhas come and watch, so don't shame me. Don't teach level
three as level five," says
Burda, and then they say Organ
taught it in the wrong order.
It's really like that every time.  When you
share your knowledge with others personally, face
to face,
then the Buddhas are attracted, just like
honey attracts bees. It
's not a story; they have
power, and it smells good
when someone shares their knowledge, and that's what attracts them.
And then they come.
Kukksi taught the new levels correctly,
very, very well.
[Music]
Secondly, at this moment, you are the
lama, you are the teacher. Then you become a
teacher. Through this, you become a teacher.
You are no less a teacher than Gesche
Michael than Kirche Michael. If you
share your knowledge correctly in the café, then
you are a real teacher. Don't think that
you are not a teacher; you are real
teachers, and the Butter are very
happy about it.
And they are there. And don't doubt
two things: if you truly share the
knowledge correctly with your
notes,
then the first is that the brothers will
come. Yes, cool, right, she did it.
When are they happy? And at
this moment, you are a real teacher.
Again Butter, again Lama,
because the new levels are real teaching.
So please, write well.  Where
have we arrived after eight years?
This is a special book called "
The Stages on the Way," said Maria
Lammering. And that means step by step.
You don't have to be a special person.
You don't have to be a monk or nun.
You can have a family, a good
job.
You should have that in your life, in your
family life, with your career. For example,
I worked in the diamond business for 19 years
while I studied for my guests. During the day,
I went to work,
earned money, helped my
family,
donated,
and then I also studied in the evenings and on
weekends. That should be it:
lead a responsible life, have a
career, a nice house, a nice
car, a great family, and
also face the responsibility and study
the Lamb. And we'll go on here for a while.
You can do both at the same time. You
should do both.
People who don't take responsibility,
people who don't take responsibility for their
lives, for a career, for their families,
won't study the Lamb responsibly either, and
you should be successful. That
should make you smart.
That should make you  Make sure you're smart, it should
be successful, so you should
have a good family. Your children
should play the drums.
We've now arrived at a specific
topic in the country,
where they talk about the problems in
this life,
and it means pack your suitcase in time
for your next
life.
Take care of your next life
because you will die.
Everyone believes they won't die. Did
their grandmother's mother die? Did
their grandmother die? Yes, I'm
speaking for myself now. Did his mother die?
That you will die? No,
and that's what we think. But it's a line:
the great-grandmother has already died,
my grandmother has died,
my mother has died, and now it's my turn. Do
n't believe it will be any
different for you. You are no different. In
this book, it says the day will
come, even though the youngest person here in
this room will also have died, and
no one will be left.
The person who wrote this book
says it in the book, and it has come true.
They all died today.
Who was the person who wrote this book?
It was my
teacher's teacher. My teacher is also already  He
died, he wrote the book,
his student died, and
his student is me, and so
the line goes on. You can be sad about it,
I don't want to think about it. If
your child is wrong, does he die? Does he
then pull the covers over his head?
He believes
the child believes that if he doesn't
see his mother, the mother can't see the child either,
and that's not how we should
behave. And that's why let's
talk about death at home. In your profession, don't talk about it too much
because it's
sad. In Thailand, then talk about death
all day because we want to
stop death. It's said
you can't shoot the enemy
if you don't know if an enemy is
the enemy. If the enemy is dead, then
we want to shoot this enemy.
People asked what your
profession is, and he said, "Karaganda,
I am the shooter of
death. Death is afraid
of me. I will shoot death." And that's what
you learn. And to
understand death, it's very good to eat lamb and beef.
Study, but don't get
depressed by it.
We're just trying to find out
who our enemy is,
and then we'll shoot him.
We're studying the problems of life. There are
six different types of
life. He knows the animals, that's
one type of life.
Then there are humans,
and then there are the shell beings.
[Music]
Bachelor, that's just superstition. There is
no hell. And now I'll tell
you something about it.
So Butter taught that
hell exists, and if you create bad karma,
then you'll end up in hell after your death.
When I went to school, when
I was 17,
we had a special
three-month course. It was by an
Italian author, a very famous
author named Auntie, and he wrote a book called The
Divine
Comedy. It has
three parts, and one part
deals with hell. We
talked about that part for a month. Every detail of hell is
described there, and it's really just like
Butter described it.
And he was never in China,
but he described the same thing.
He  I've seen hell,
and that's why you shouldn't tell me it's
a Chinese superstition. You can find the
same description in the classics, in
the European classics,
and some people say it's the
best book ever written in Europe. It's
the exact
same description:
after you die, you can be reborn as an animal, or
if you're lucky, as a
human. But you could also end up in
hell,
and the fourth
possibility is to become an animal.
Then there are two types of
superheroes, like Iron Man or Spider-Man,
and there are two different
types: the little superheroes and the big ones.
So Spider-Man is a little hero
and a big one. And these
beings also exist. So there are six
possibilities. Of
course, we want to be reborn as humans;
we don't want to end up in hell;
we don't want to end up as animals.
And then there are the hungry
ghosts. We don't want to be ghosts either;
we want to be reborn as humans at the very least.
And now I'll tell you something very
special.
So if you understand the lesson well,
then you have a  A guarantee
that you won't be reborn on a lower plane after you
died of the Douro, that it's like a contract
with butter. So if you really
understand the majority reasonably well,
then after your death you won't be
reborn in the lower realms.
You won't be reborn as the beast,
not in hell. You can't
become a hungry ghost either.
It's impossible. That's a guarantee.
And the best way to teach is, of
course, with a pen. He's often
heard me teach the pen. There's
a very famous example: when
I was in Singapore. I've been going to Singapore every year for
ten or nine years.
We need two
[music],
and every year I teach the pen
on the first day, right at the beginning.
After I've been there for eight years, even in the
eighth year, I explained the pen for five
minutes. Then, after the lecture,
a man came up to me, and he wasn't from
Singapore, he was from Europe. This happened to
Michael. What I think is, you're getting
old. Why do you say you repeat
everything? What have I repeated?  Every time
you teach the pen, eight times
you've taught the pen now, you forgot that, no,
I didn't forget,
I know I've already taught you the pen,
but you don't use it, you don't know, that's why
I have to teach the pen today,
why
[Music],
if you understand the pen reasonably well, so what I'll
teach you in the next ten minutes, then you can't be
reborn in hell, you can't be reborn as
the beast,
you are not a hungry ghost,
it's important, so if you're at home,
for example, to the Czech Republic, and
you're sitting next to a handsome young man like
Stanley, you can do that, and
now, where are you from? I'm already there too, because
where are you going?
But I'm flying to Thailand, why did
I ever tell the story of the pen,
and then share it with other
people, why,
if you explain it really well,
then they can't be reborn in hell anymore,
and that's
pretty cool, I would say, you're helping
these people, if he asks, are
you into organic juice or
water? I have the emails from
So, I always have a pen with me, that's it.
We have a
special university in America, and the second one
will be in Singapore, I think.
[Applause]
And there we teach how to teach the
pen, and there are 18 parts on
how to teach the pen correctly. I wonder
if he'll find all 18 parts. You
can go to the country class after your afternoon nap. I don't care
because I don't teach in the afternoon,
but now in the morning, concentrate.
You can help someone's life so many times, so
learn how to teach the pen.
Two things when you
teach: number one should
be correct, and number two, it should be fun.
Okay, and I'm not like that. I have a
friend from the Czech Republic.
She always looks at me like this. Don't
be so serious.
Life is short and very... Parents
know that. Ten minutes ago they were
20, and then...
and now I'm 65. What happened?
Life goes by quickly. Of course,
we have many problems in life. Everyone
here in the room has very specific problems.
Can we call a problem competition? Basement...
I can't smile. Why? I
have such big...  Problems,
should we call out the problem competitor?
Someone here has cancer.
The mother died two days ago.
I have to call her after
this class.
Everyone has problems.
[Music]
We can be people who
have problems and therefore can't smile.
But we can also be a person who
has problems and still smiles. The
second type of person is clearly better. Do
you have problems? Oh yeah, rather serious
problems. Very serious problems.
Why are you smiling? Is it for what reason? Just
smile.
Everyone has problems. If you teach the pen
or vice versa, finished.
If you teach the pen, ask
your friends to give each other answers.
I'm asking questions now and he's
answering. More please. I think it's
important to tell people to
just give natural answers that
come to mind. Don't think too much about it. It's
not a philosophy
class. Is it a pen class? Give me
good answers. What is a pen? Look, there was
a little dog. I'm going to
stand up now and then show
the dog the pen. What will the dog do with the
pen? Yes, the goods
The dog barely pulls a pen on it. No, what does
the dog see? A toy to chew on.
Hardly. Who is right, the human or
the dog? Both are right. Why? The
dog chews on it and enjoys it, and a
stupid human doesn't chew on my pen.
You are then, he says, and you are such a
stupid human. It tastes so good. Why are
you writing with it? Don't
write with a pen. Don't write with my
toy. Can I have my pen and
not write with a pen? It's
okay. And now the big question is, if
I put the pen here now, and
all the humans leave the room, and
all the dogs leave the room,
and nobody is there at this time,
it is at this time a pen
or a toy, nothing.
You want to understand the apprenticeship. 123, that
is the apprenticeship. That is the apprenticeship.
Hyde, at this time, what is it? It is
a toy and a pen, nothing. That
is the apprenticeship.
[Music] There are
three famous false ideas about
the apprenticeship.
I'll show you number one:
majority black, everything is black.
Is the teaching right? No,
it doesn't help her. Black, black,
black,
it doesn't help her. You learn this emptiness.
Hyde,
you won't be a successful person.
You won't have a family.
You won't be healthy when you
're 65. You'll just be.
That's not the majority, not black. Keep
observing the mind. The thought goes
from right to left,
but don't think. Just let go, just let it pass. That's not
empty. Haid, many say
just think nothing. What is that? Can you do that stuff
if you don't think? I show that. I show that. I have
an empty phone. You saw my phone.
I just saw it. Do you understand? If that's
karma, if you try not to
think about anything, you'll always
lose your phone.
Forgetfulness. That's not empty. Haid,
and the third famous one, is it wrong? Someone is
hurting you. Someone is hitting you.
No happiness, no sadness,
nothing. That's empty. Is it a totally
stupid idea? When you see the mother picture, they do
n't look like that. They smile, they're cheerful, happy.
That's not empty.
Haid, what is truth? When the dogs
leave the room, when  The people
leave the room.
It's not a pen, it's not a
toy, it's empty.
Now, when the person comes back into the room,
and the one standing over there is called
Lee, and I look at the thing, at that
moment it changes. What happens? It
becomes a pen. At that
moment,
the Heydt pen comes again, the majority. At that moment
it changes. Before, what? And now
it's a pen. When does that happen? The
teacher, and now it becomes a pen. How does
it become a pen? How does it become a pen?
It must come from me. Why? If he
comes in underneath, but the same empty
thing becomes a toy. It must come from me.
The pen comes from the person. The toy comes from the
dog. Comes from the pen. Yes or no? No,
that's the proof.
And if the pen came from the pen,
then the dog would write
love poems to his dog friend with it,
what a pretty tail
she has. That's why the pen comes from me. A
very famous mistake.
Some people say, you say positive
thinking, always be positive. Everything comes from
you.
Then, if you want a diamond, we wish...
Something, I don't want a pen,
I want a diamond.
Everything comes from me. They have diamond, diamond.
You can also
speak Mani Padme Hum, and Mani Padme Hum,
Armani Pat Baum, the Armani Mani Padme Hum
diamond. You can use it to make tablets.
Diamonds come from me, and Mani Padme
Hum, Mani Padme Hum. Yes, still a pen.
Why? It comes from you, but
something forces you
to see a pen.
You have no choice. What forces you to
see a pen? If you incite the seed
in your mind, then when
you enter the room,
the seed opens, then a small picture comes
out. A pen picture comes out of his
mind, 65 per second.
It goes so fast that you can't perceive it.
If you meditate a lot,
you'll see how that happens. I'm sure I'll open it.
Then you see how the image emerges from the
seed, how many? 65 per second.
When you watch a video online,
when you're in the Itanium Hotelbiz area,
the internet isn't particularly good
here,
then you see the individual images.
That means you slow down; the images
should normally be 24 per second,
but when the internet is slow,
and the same thing happens with your
mind when you meditate, when you meditate a lot,
then you can see how the mind
opens. Then you can see how 65 seeds
open per second. On the internet, it's 24
per second, but in real life, it's 65.
Why is that? You need extra seeds
for smell, taste, and touch. A
live video that opens 65 per
second.
These seeds open,
and what does dependent emergence mean?
Everything is dependent on its seeds,
and emergence means the pen begins.
That's dependent emergence. The seed
opens, opens. What is
the learning period now?
The learning period is the place that creates the space
so that the image can overlay itself.
If there were no majority, then there wouldn't be
one there.  Place where the
image of the toy could be projected onto it.
The apprenticeship allows
the dog seed to open as a toy.
The apprenticeship allows the human
seed to open a pen.
If you know how to plant a seed,
then you can achieve anything
you want. Why?
Everything in your life comes from tameness.
Everything comes from seeds.
I think my teacher taught me for 20 years,
and then I talked to him. Did
I teach you the teachers? Yes. Did
I teach you seeds?
Yes. What percentage comes
from everything together? Now you are ready
for a final test. Olam, final
test, depending on New York City, and start
a business and use your
knowledge of seeds and find out if you
can make money.
And if you do, then you have
passed the test,
and if not, then you know you didn't.
Together, you didn't really understand.
It's really a pretty strange final test,
and I did it, and
you know we created the biggest diamond
business in the world.
We started with three diamonds,
and
they were smaller than sugar cornyn,
which you your  You put your mind into it
and later we processed 300,000 diamonds
a day. I had no business
experience. Number two, I
also don't like doing business, no
experience, and I'm just not
really an entrepreneur, but it was
my final test that the seed
test. So if the pen
comes from seed, then money also comes from
seed. The husband also comes from seed.
Your body,
the 65-year-old body, also comes from
seed, and you can change everything. That's
the meaning of the Heydt. I give
you four choices. Number one, the
majority is black. Number two, the
Heydt is thinking of nothing, no. Number
three, no course, no drums, a
happiness, no
sadness, always neutral. That's the teaching.
Number 1, the fourth, empty.
The biggest diamond business in the
world. A 65-year-old body is a
young body. Why? That comes from you. Understood, understand,
learn, simply how to
plant seeds. Understood. What is
the next step now?
We have to learn how to plant a seed.
Ready, many volunteers,
many volunteers. I have $100,
forget it.
I want to make $
1000, want to get $1000.
Those who ask don't get anything, and those who do
n't ask get anything.
I want to plant a seed for $1000
now. This isn't a
demonstration. This is how a bachelor earns his
salary. This is real
life.
I'm really planting a seed. Why do
you do this every day?
Because I need money. I have to do it. I
have no choice. I have $100.
I want to teach you how to
plant. There are
four steps, and you can
say, "But you already taught this last year." I don't care. I don't want
her to end up
in hell. I want him to make
progress. If he understands the pen, if
you understand the $100,
then you're protected.
If you have a car accident in Bangkok
and never get home, then you're
protected. Understood?
I just have to do it,
and I'll keep doing it for the rest of my life.
The four steps to plant a seed.
You're welcome to record me, but...  Do
n't do it in public restrooms, it's
not legal to do that, that
's the rule, so please pay attention to
everyone here. I could gladly record it.
Is it actually a good idea? Now here we go.
I think this lady here.
Hello, what's your name? Hello Emily, will
you help me plant a seed?
Yes, thank you. I'm happy. She's helping me
plant a seed. Seed planting
has four steps. Don't forget, if you
learn this, you can easily
start a big business.
You can still dance ballet at 65. You
can create a great family.
Learn the four steps, use the
four steps. Step number one: you
have to decide what you want.
In my example, today
I want $1000. Do my goal
today, earn $1000. That's
step number one. Maybe a
first step is the
stone. Higher goal:
What is a much higher goal? I want
my husband to do the dishes every night. That's
a very high goal.
Or maybe I want to be healthy.
I want to be beautiful. Or I want
a peaceful mind.
I want the whole world to be real.
You decide. You can plant any
seed, but today, for
demonstration purposes, we'll plant
$1,000. Step number two: You need
a partner and a seed to
plant.
It's impossible to plant a seed
if you don't do it with another
person.
Okay, I'm so shy, I do
n't want to talk to others. Then forget
it. Then you can't complete the four steps.
You can be humble and poor,
so of course you also have to have some strength.
Go to the other person, Emily. Will you help
me make a thousand dollars? Yes, well, then
you just do
step number two. You need a
partner to plant seeds.
Step number three: You have to
plant it together. How do you plant the
seed, Emily? Then raise a hand. Then
I'll take the $100.
I'll place your hand and I'll
close the hand. Then with love and with
love, I say one, two, three things
completely: I have planted a seed.
How is that karma? You have to know how to
create a karma.
You can say, 'Here you can already...'
Saying that it's the same whether you're dealing with karma
or seeds, it's the same. But
how do you plant the seed? You have to
watch yourself doing it.
You have to hear yourself
saying something good. I'm watching, yes, I'm
planting the seed, Emily.
This sound meets my own
and creates an imprint. And after two
hours, this impression,
this imprint, then becomes a
chamber, and it will open and
make a pen, or it opens
and generates $1000.
When I gave the $100 to her hand
and opened my hand, I let go,
and this image
hits my eye and touches my mind,
and that creates the tame in
my mind.
Now the seed is planted. Thank you.
Step number four: If you do
n't know the fourth step, then you have
planted the seed,
but it won't ripen for 100 years. You'll
get $1000,
but it's too late.
We don't want to wait 100 years. You
have to water the seed.
You have to...  Watering seeds, like this, you water
the seeds.
It's a very special meditation,
Max, not like when
my teacher taught me that under me.
It was after the
car accident.
He had the car accident before I
met him. After hair, and during the
car accident, his throat was
injured. That's why he always spoke like Star Wars.
You have to speak like this. Now it's time
for step number four. What is it? What is
the fourth step called? I
asked. Café meditation. And how do
I do it? Don't sit like that,
Mom. You taught me to
meditate like this. Don't do it.
What do you want? What I do is a
very special motto. I'll show you the
motorcycle. Yeah, then okay. It
was stopped. These are moderate. And now there's
a very special café
meditation - moderate.
[Music]
Okay, café meditation, café mudra. Man, does
he do the café meditation before he
goes to bed, before you fall asleep? Why?
His mind will be occupied with it all night while you
sleep. You were generating 1000 dollars
while you sleep. Very, very good.
Your mind cooks it during the  Sleep
and then you have to think about all the good things
you did today. We
love to dwell on our problems
while we sleep because
500 people in this room say, "My
problem is the worst of all." Yes,
you can smile, you don't have
my problem.
My problem is really serious.
When I go to bed,
that's a very special time.
I can always go over
my problem again and again: my marriage,
my children aren't learning,
my boss doesn't like me, he likes
my colleague much better. Then
you'll spend the whole
night... bad seeds... don't do it, don't worry.
Before
falling asleep, the best time
to worry is in the early morning
after the sun has risen
because sunlight has a very
special power.
It makes the big problems small.
Darkness before you sleep, then
you're tired. It's really a very
bad time to think about your problems.
I can't
dwell on my problem.
Yes, should I... when should I
do my problem meditation? At
what time? Do it in the morning. Why?
Because then they will
grow smaller. Never think about them at night.
Emily thinks of her face tonight when
Michael goes to bed. I can't help but think of
Emily's face, the way she
smiled.
I think she's celebrating with her friends tonight. A
very special
dinner
for your friends tonight,
and she looks so happy. Before
you go to bed, think of all the good things
you did today.
But what did I do today? I didn't do anything
good today. What did
you do yesterday?
Okay,
manufacturer, I didn't do anything good yesterday either. Okay,
then ten years ago you did
something nice.
Yes, yes, yes, I did something good.
Then think about that too. Okay, that's it.
If you think about it and are
happy about it, then that seed will
ripen faster because being happy about it is like
watering a flower. No matter what good thing
you did ten years ago,
bachelor.
But God, ten years ago was
much worse than today. What am I supposed to do
then? Have you
seen anyone else do something good?
Jasmin and her team work so hard
in Thailand.  Absolutely fantastic, so
happy about this, and now I'm going to share a
secret with you:
Jasmin and his team, Tim and his team, have
created the Hama Meter Pass paradise here in Thailand.
They have really, really
planted great, good seeds. They've been working for a
year to prepare everything for us,
and I have good news for you.
[Music]
If you do a coffee meditation about their
good seeds, then you get ten
percent off. That's a good deal,
I'd say. That's good karma. Don't worry, don't worry,
they do
n't lose ten percent,
it simply becomes 110. And don't worry, it doesn't make
anything good for you, but you can do what
you did today. Then think of other
people who have done good, you get
ten percent of it.
And today, I think the ten percent
from Carl of Jasmin's team today is
more good karma. Vegas, understood? The
hit song, I'm sure now,
everyone teaches it, really good
karma. January, preparing for 500 people,
is also good karma.
Which one should I do a coffee meditation with now?
Of course, both of them,
no problem at all. Do you have extra karma?
Created
[Music]
can rejoice in both if you
understood what I
taught today about the pen and
taming, then it's almost guaranteed that
you won't be reborn in hell. That's why
I say almost, I'm going to
explain it in depth now because you came to
Thailand.
If you think about the seed that
makes the pen, then you're almost guaranteed
that if you die today—that's
possible—then you won't end up in the
lower realms.
Why do you say almost? There's one more
teaching you need to understand to
protect yourself.
[Music]
These are the last five percent of
teachers, but you need to understand them, so that's why
I'm going to teach them to you now.
Never forget
[Music],
so spend your teaching time in Starbucks,
partly watching all the brothers with someone.
Then don't forget the last five percent. What are
the five percent that
truly protect other people?
Here's an example: Bachelor, this
morning you taught the lion dance.
You said close your eyes,
said concentrate on the
air conditioning, and then you said
concentrate.
During meditation, I had only
one thought about your heartbeat: cake, cake, cake, heads, doughnuts,
what's for
lunch?
I asked my mind to
meditate,
but my mind doesn't follow me. I
spoke to my mind, "Now
we meditate," and then the mind says, "Okay." And I said
to the mind again, "
Schiller says we should listen to the air
conditioning now," and he said, "We are
concentrating on the heart like this.
Can you do that?"
You're speaking to your mind in that
moment, and then the mind says, "Yes, yes, yes, let's do it.
In silence, lower the
heartbeat. Okay, yes, yes, the mind is speaking to
you. I'll get it ready. Now we start knocking, knocking, cake, cake, cake, cake, cake, Kurds, good, be still, okay, okay,
cake."
You know you don't think about
cake all day, but when the bachelor
starts meditating, then only
cake comes to mind. It's madness.
Why? Because you hate thinking about cake in your mind.
You're
not the one who speaks in your mind;
you're the listener. What?  Do you always tell your
husband
you can't
talk and listen at the same time?
Just stop talking for a minute and
listen to me. I'll tell you something: you
can speak and
listen at the same time. And that was in your mind. Either
you are the one speaking
or you are the one listening, because then,
and your husband is proof
that you can't be both.
Either a husband speaks or your
husband listens.
In your mind, it's the same: you listen to
his thoughts.
You can't speak in your mind.
Hescheler, who then speaks in my mind?
Who speaks in my mind? His seeds.
The seeds speak. That's not you.
Your seeds speak in your mind. There is
no you. In your mind,
your mind speaks. It's empty.
Your mind is he, that you
speak in it. Listen. Listen. How protects
you?
It's simply practical. Even who
speaks in your mind together. The
flag speaks in one mind. Is there
someone who speaks in one mind, and
no seed is just because I protect
you from hell right now? Right now, is there
someone who speaks in your mind?
That's not  From seed comes no
and that is knowledge from the heath that
protects you
now you have the protection is it cool is
that cool yes is there a pen in
my mind fit now woke up is there
a pen in my mind yes of
course is there a pen in my mind
that arises from my name yes of course
if I need more pen seed how do
I create these pens together in
my mind okay that creates you pen seed
in my mind I'll do it again is there
a pen in my mind who
made the screaming children
they also come from me
maybe I need to be more polite is there a pen
in my mind is there
a pen in my head that
comes from my seed yes now a big
big question is there a pen in
my head that doesn't come from seed
no what is truth a pen it
protects me halfway from hell
but we need a little more
done
[Music]
can you hear in these minutes how
your mind thinks the atra do you hear
thoughts in your mind that from  Seeds
are produced, yes, of course,
all thoughts come from seeds. If you
listen to your own mind, then
you hear how thoughts, seeds, open in your
mind. Last question: are there
conversations in your mind that are not
caused by seeds? No,
impossible.
That is your emptiness, and if you
truly understand that, then you are
protected forever. Then
you can never be reborn in hell again. That is
impossible. Is that cool?
Okay, done.
Now we can start with the new thing.
20 minutes.
I know you're tired. I know
you've been here since yesterday, and I'm
so happy you're here. I
think he's really cool. Time for another 20
minutes,
and then we'll have a
nice long break because he wants to take a
break too, of course. Another
20 minutes,
and then we'll do the book. My
teacher taught me this book word for word,
and that's how I do it too. That's how
I teach as well. We will
go through the book word for word. Slowly,
enjoy the fries because if you
pump quickly...  Then you'll
get an upset stomach from it.
This book must be enjoyed very slowly. Savor
it bit by bite and do
n't try to eat it too quickly.
Word for word, China.
That sounds really cool, that after I
die, why a human being has a
human reincarnation if it's possible for
me to be reborn as a superhero?
I think I'd like to be that superhero.
I can be a small hero like
Spiderman or a big hero. Back in
Hollywood, they say all
American movies are made there.
If you want to earn a hundred million dollars,
then make a
superhero movie. Always make
superhero movies, not emotional ones,
because you don't earn
money with those. If you really
want to earn real money, then make a
superhero movie. Why? Because people
love them. I love them too. I do
n't watch many movies,
but I always watch superhero movies.
Why? Because Spiderman is a
really cool guy. It's really cool.
When I was a kid, we had
Spiderman comics, and I lived them.
I read them every day, and then
I asked my husband, "Can I
become Spiderman too?" When I grow up, I
want to be Spiderman.  To be completely human, and of
course, Mom,
how did Spiderman become Spiderman? And
then she said he was
bitten by a special spider,
a radioactive spider. Okay,
Mom, every time I'm not
beautiful now, or when I'm a spider, well,
I know myself, and I think 100
spiders have bitten me, and nothing happened,
just five scratches.
We all love these superheroes, yes, and
they really exist, and that's why
we love these movies, because we go to these
places, you know, in our past lives.
The reason you like these movies so much is
because you remember them from
his past lives. You were exactly like
that, and now you're just a human. Of
course, it's possible that you
say to yourself, "That's totally cool. If I die,
then I want to be reborn in one of these
superhero places."
They have too much power, even more
powerful than Iron Man. What do they do so
simply because they want to have fun? Does
he also have moments in China?  We
played marbles, yeah, you know that one?
We lived it when we were 7, 6, or
7. Back then,
marbles were banned at school because we wasted too much time on them.
So, these superheroes, which we also
call gods, love to
play too, but the marbles are whole
planets
that have superpowers. So, it's
really possible that some people think, "
I would love to be reborn as a superhero to
play marbles with planets because I
really like that." But the problem is, even
in this world, there are very specific
problems in this god world. We can be
reborn there
if you give Emily a lot of money, if you
give Emily a lot of money,
if you play the Lion Dance fruit, the
first eight stages over and over again
without
going to the new ninth stage. Then you create
certain seeds to be reborn as a god.
That actually sounds pretty cool, but there's
a problem with it,
and now we're right in the book.
They talk about the problems of these
planets. Murnau learns about the problems that
these  Gods have because then
you might decide that you don't want to be reborn there. I'd
rather be a mother, or it helps
more people in the book.
Now he's talking in the book about exactly
these particular problems of these gods. I'm going to
read you the Tibetan.
He doesn't know the language, of course,
but it's a very powerful seed in
your mind. Don't worry,
Hescheler, it bores me when you
use this old language. I do
n't have an intention; I'm
trying to plant a seed in your mind.
Now it begins.
[Music]
The famous line. Many here in the room have
scarves around them. Maybe if you don't have one,
you should get one tomorrow so
you don't eat. And there are many
different qualities of a
scarf.
I was in Ukraine. Who was there?
All my Ukrainian friends.
I was at the Prima Palace Hotel, and I
bought a scarf there for my
old lady.
It was a shop; it's very, very expensive,
and I didn't know it.
I went in.
Now I saw this scarf.
Perfect, perfect for my old lady.
Yesterday we also bought her some things in Chuncheon.
I love shopping for her, like pink
stuff and red sleep deprivation, and I like to
buy
[music] for her
at the Premium Palace Hotel, and then
I said I want this scarf.
She said okay, team, went, and then
she said 3000. I said
Ukrainian currency, yen per dollar, and
1,443, 1000 dollars. I think the color is
n't that great.
Why are we talking about this? Listen, if
you wear a 3000 dollar scarf for a day,
then you use up a lot of
seeds. They are very expensive seeds. You
use up these 3000 dollar seeds in
one day.
If you have a cheap scarf with a 100
dollar bill,
it might not be as comfortable,
but the seeds are also cheaper. You
only use up the 100 dollar seeds. I'm
not telling you to buy very cheap
clothes,
I'm not saying that. Yeah, yeah, I think
you should really buy nice clothes,
and you should also buy some for
others.  Do you all always have enough seeds to
have beautiful clothes,
all you husbands here?
When you drive home with your wife
and she sees something beautiful
at the airport, you mustn't say, "
Michael says the expensive stars
consume a lot." Don't say that
to your wife. The Swiss guy only
said that means wearing cheap clothes.
I didn't say that, but I did say
the husband should buy the most beautiful
clothes for his wife because
then he plants a lot of good seeds.
But these gods consume a lot of
good things
the moment they murmur with
the planet.
For that, you need a lot of good things in
this world to be there for a day.
Very, very expensive, a lot, a lot came, but it's
consumed there. So what happens then?
[Music]
Then the Great Lama said, "Your
task in this life is not to
consume good karma, but your
task is to create good karma." So
your task is not
to have the most expensive car, the most expensive house,
the most expensive shoes. You shouldn't
be a karma consumer, but a
karma producer.  You have a choice in
your life:
you can be the kind of person who
consumes seeds, or you can
be the kind who produces seeds. And our
job as Buddhists is to produce more seeds,
not to use them up.
I didn't say
he couldn't buy a Tesla. I didn't say that.
I didn't say that.
I only said don't
consume more seeds than you
produce. Buy a Tesla and take
lots of people with you. Then
you'll have produced more Tesla seeds than you
need. Jack, put on nice
clothes, beautiful clothes, and invite your
friends to a café and teach them how to use the
pen. Because then there will be 100 brothers
in the café watching you.
She teaches the pen,
yes, yes, and she does it really cool,
and she looks really cool too,
very, very beautiful.
With that, you produce many new seeds. You
make the brothers happy. And Pusack, put
on nice clothes. Wear the little
clothes when you explain the pen, but
produce more seeds than you need.
How do you produce more seeds than you
need?  Seeds are mental. I
teach my friends the pen.
You're in the café today.
Then you have to tell your husband, "
Excuse me, I have to..." in front of the
coffee shop. The pen was explained in the morning.
It's okay if I buy a new dress,
and then he says to someone, "Why
not for me? I'm going to the café today.
I'm teaching the pen, and all the
brothers will be there.
I have to look good if that's his
motivation." And that's really true.
It's no joke. If that's your
motivation, then you'll
produce more seeds with that motivation. How
you consume when you buy the dress—
smart shopping—
and everyone asked me. This happened
this year in Germany.
I wanted to say "
Good morning, how are you?" again. And I
taught it there for the first time since ten. The
new level is always presented in Germany
because Silvia founded it in Germany,
and I believe she has also
published more books than any other
country.
Thank you, Silvia. The roper will see how
not to get angry anymore. You
should really come when we teach it in
China or Singapore,
and there  Many people have asked me,
Schiller,
what is level 11?
It's always a secret. What is level 11? What
is this? Help, I'll tell you, but
nobody counts advanced shopping.
How do you shop? How do you shop in such a way
that you generate more seeds with it? Are
you consumed when you buy a new shirt
for the lamps? Class, how much did
it cost?
[Music]
How many seeds have I burned in these three
hours by wearing a
new shirt? I have to generate more seeds
so that consumers like
in your mind... Okay, I
taught for three hours because I have the pen
and the courts. The Buddhas have to come
because I'm saving 500 people from hell.
The Buddhas have to come.
Then I should really have a pretty hand.
If I think like that, then I will
make more good seeds than I
spend. The student didn't say
bachelor, didn't say buy, not
that loyalty, the expensive clothes. The bachelor
said no matter how many seeds you spend,
you always have to make more seeds.
And what's the problem?  Up there in the
gods' realm, they do
n't understand the pen; they
simply consume the seeds of every god.
Every god who dies goes straight to
hell.
Why? Because they simply
use up their good seeds, and they don't produce
new ones. It's cool.
Thanks
for today. Are we at the end?